<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<APT_LetterLabelHypnosisFailed>Hypnosis failed on {PAWN_nameDef}</APT_LetterLabelHypnosisFailed>
	<APT_LetterHypnosisFailed>A revenant failed to hypnotize {PAWN_nameDef} due to their lack of psychic sensitivity. The experience has left them feeling shaken, but otherwise unharmed.\n\nThe revenant uses psychic powers to twist the perceptions of those around it, making itself invisible. However, it can still be hunted by following the black smears that it leaves. The revenant will be revealed if hit by explosive weapons, firefoam, EMPs, fire, or disruptor flares.\n\nIf not killed, the revenant will continue to hypnotize new victims.</APT_LetterHypnosisFailed>
	
	<APT_LetterLabelHypnosisMild>{PAWN_nameDef} resisted hypnosis</APT_LetterLabelHypnosisMild>
	<APT_LetterHypnosisMild>A revenant attempted to hypnotize {PAWN_nameDef}, but failed to fully incapacitate them due to their limited psychic sensitivity. They are plagued with waking nightmares and a cacophony of hateful voices fills their mind, yet they are still able to function at a diminished capacity.\n\nKilling the revenant will end the hypnosis.\n\nThe revenant uses psychic powers to twist the perceptions of those around it, making itself invisible. However, it can still be hunted by following the black smears that it leaves. The revenant will be revealed if hit by explosive weapons, firefoam, EMPs, fire, or disruptor flares.\n\nIf not killed, the revenant will continue to hypnotize new victims.</APT_LetterHypnosisMild>

	<APT_LetterLabelHypnosisSevere>{PAWN_nameDef} hypnotized</APT_LetterLabelHypnosisSevere>
	<APT_LetterHypnosisSevere>{PAWN_nameDef} has been hypnotized by a revenant and remains linked to it. The effects are unusually severe due to their increased psychic sensitivity. They lay curled in the fetal position, clawing at their skin and raving about otherworldly horrors only they can see.\n\nKilling the revenant will end the hypnosis, but some effects will linger afterwards.\n\nThe revenant uses psychic powers to twist the perceptions of those around it, making itself invisible. However, it can still be hunted by following the black smears that it leaves. The revenant will be revealed if hit by explosive weapons, firefoam, EMPs, fire, or disruptor flares.\n\nIf not killed, the revenant will continue to hypnotize new victims.</APT_LetterHypnosisSevere>

	<APT_LetterLabelHypnosisExtreme>{PAWN_nameDef} hypnotized</APT_LetterLabelHypnosisExtreme>
	<APT_LetterHypnosisExtreme>{PAWN_nameDef} has been hypnotized by a revenant and remains linked to it. The effects are especially severe due to their increased psychic sensitivity. They lay motionless on the ground, eyes wide and face frozen in a look of utter terror. The only signs of life are their shallow breathing, faint heartbeat, and the tears that occasionally creep down their face.\n\nKilling the revenant will end the hypnosis, but some effects will linger long afterwards.\n\nThe revenant uses psychic powers to twist the perceptions of those around it, making itself invisible. However, it can still be hunted by following the black smears that it leaves. The revenant will be revealed if hit by explosive weapons, firefoam, EMPs, fire, or disruptor flares.\n\nIf not killed, the revenant will continue to hypnotize new victims.</APT_LetterHypnosisExtreme>

 	<APT_MessageAwokenKilledVictim>The awoken corpse has crushed {PAWN_nameDef}'s skull.</APT_MessageAwokenKilledVictim>
</LanguageData>